[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common name is used to refer to the scavenging animals, representatives of the order Opiliones?", "correct_answer": "Harvestmen", "incorrect_answers": ["Waterbugs", "Sweepers", "Bumblebees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Back to the Future, the building where the diner was located in 1955, houses what type of studio in 1985?", "correct_answer": "Aerobics studio", "incorrect_answers": ["Art studio", "Recording studio", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The author of the book that inspired A Christmas Story, Jean Shepherd, narrated the film.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In baseball, when a quarterback throws a pass, the ball follows what type of path?", "correct_answer": "Parabola", "incorrect_answers": ["Ray", "Point", "Line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what did Brooks thank the player he cut just before the start of the Olympics in the movie Miracle?", "correct_answer": "For giving him his very best", "incorrect_answers": ["For giving him a lift to practice", "For making his decision easier", "For taking the decision like a man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following paths is one of the two most popular climbing routes to Mount Everest?", "correct_answer": "The southeast ridge from Nepal", "incorrect_answers": ["The south ridge from Tibet", "The east ridge from Pakistan", "The west ridge from India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Krypton?", "correct_answer": "Kr", "incorrect_answers": ["Kp", "K", "Ky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Camille Mitchell, Katharine Isabelle, and Jessica Parker Kennedy, who appeared in Another Cinderella Story, have also starred in this TV series.", "correct_answer": "Smallville", "incorrect_answers": ["Charmed", "One Tree Hill", "Buffy the Vampire Slayer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the actress who starred in Vanilla Sky, Dont Move, Volaverunt and All about my Mother?", "correct_answer": "Penelope Cruz", "incorrect_answers": ["Yolanda Alvarez", "Lucia Sanchez", "Salma Hayek"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which words from the movie Grease were delivered by Kenickie, the character played by Jeff Conaway ?", "correct_answer": "Youre cruisin for a bruisin", "incorrect_answers": ["I feel like a defective typewriter", "But its true! Ive just had the best summer of my life, and now I have to go away", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these four countries does not border the Red Sea.", "correct_answer": "Oman", "incorrect_answers": ["Jordan", "Egypt", "Sudan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The geological area called The Ring of Fire is located along the borders of the Pacific Ocean.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]